buzz-hut.com 2017-12-04

# Privacy Policy | Buzz-Hut

This privacy policy details the efforts we take to protect your information. We’re committed to protecting your information. We will only ask you to provide it as a means of identifying you, and it will only be used in the ways specified by this privacy policy. This policy may undergo subtle changes when we update this page. You should periodically check this page to see if we’ve recently altered the policy.

## Security

We’re dedicated to securing your information to keep you safe. We have added suitable electronic, physical and managerial safeguards to protect the information that we collect from the Web.

## How We Use Cookies

A cookie is a small file that needs permission to be added to your computer’s hard drive. After you agree, the cookie is added and it assists with Web traffic as well as letting you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow Web applications to personalize your experience by tailoring themselves to the things you like and the things you don’t. Cookies gather and maintain information about you and the pages you visit, so we can keep track of our Web traffic. This allows us to make the necessary adjustments to keep the site relevant. Cookies never give us access to your personal information or access to your computer. Most Web browsers automatically allow cookies to access your hard drive, but you can turn cookies off in your settings. However, taking this step will adversely affect your Web surfing experience. Cookies are also used to show you our ads when you visit various websites. You can opt out of Google’s cookies via this link.

Third-party vendors such as Google use cookies to tailor ads to you based upon the sites you visit. Google also uses the double-click cookie to allow itself and its partners to send you custom ads based upon your visits to this and other sites. The following link allows you to opt out of the double-click cookie-based ads.

## Links to Other Sites

Our site contains links to other sites to help you more easily navigate the Web. However, clicking these links takes you away from our site to sites where our privacy policy is no longer enforced. We have no jurisdiction over the other websites and assume no responsibility for the information they collect.
